Double-click to open the British Files folder and find Scene Details.
Open the Adding Smoking folder.
Double-click on Dress Smoking or drag it to the 2D or 3D window.
Select the fourth tool bar in the 2D or 3D tool bar.
Double-click to lock the outline line.
Use the loop outline tool to select the base line.
Press the Rewind button to loop the base line to the inner line.
Press the Rewind button to drag the 2D line opens to the inner line.
Use the Rewind button to lock the outline line.
Press the Rewind button to lock the상 panel.
Press the Rewind button to lock the powers hustle button to the inner line.
In the Suiteели printer, use theetos drifters tool.
Pick a fountain icon beside forecasting to divide the value to 50%.
Use a foundation object meant for clips.
Someone who кошающphon
Open up Pl Flower!
On the top and bottom of the screen, select the 4th button in the 2D vertical tool bar, and click to lock the screen.
Unlock the previously locked screen.
Use the editor tool to select the upper and lower screen of the front and back panels.
In the audio editor, select the negative frame next to the elastic, and set the value to 50%.
In the 3D window, select the front and back panels.
On the right-hand side of the panel, click and select the node in the left-hand column.
Turn on the simulation, and apply the settings to the 3D costume.
In the object window, find Silk , and drag it into the object window .
Since the mold has a good extension and weight, if the fabric is made of a foot-thick branch,
such as cowhide, the wrinkles will be more detailed.
Open the simulation,
and apply the settings to the 3D window.
In the 3D tool bar, select the 3D tool.
On the top and bottom of the panel, select the double-click to create a fixed point.
In the 3D tool bar, select the tool to improve the quality of the costume.
Click to confirm.
Turn on the simulation, and apply the settings to the 3D costume.
In the 3d tool bar, choose the 4
wheel.
这里应用到3D服装中
JPEG